http://www.yeswatch.com/wrist-watch/equilibrium/terms-conditions-privacy-policy.html

READ
SHOP
Terms & Conditions / Privacy Policy
Wild Seed Inc DBA YES watch Terms of Service and Privacy Policy
1. Terms
By accessing the website at http://yeswatch.com,
you are agreeing to be bound by these terms of service, all
applicable laws and regulations, and agree that you are responsible
for compliance with any applicable local laws. If you do not agree
with any of these terms, you are prohibited from using or accessing
this site. The materials contained in this website are protected by
applicable copyright and trademark law.
2. Use License
Permission is granted to temporarily download one copy of the materials
(information or software) on Wild Seed Inc DBA YES watch's website
for personal, non-commercial transitory viewing only. This is the
grant of a license, not a transfer of title, and under this license
you may not:
modify
or copy the materials;
use
the materials for any commercial purpose, or for any public display
(commercial or non-commercial);
attempt
to decompile or reverse engineer any software contained on Wild
Seed Inc DBA YES watch's website;
remove
any copyright or other proprietary notations from the materials; or
transfer
the materials to another person or "mirror" the materials
on any other server.
This license shall automatically terminate if you violate any of these
restrictions and may be terminated by Wild Seed Inc DBA YES watch at
any time. Upon terminating your viewing of these materials or upon
the termination of this license, you must destroy any downloaded
materials in your possession whether in electronic or printed
format.
3. Disclaimer
The materials on Wild Seed Inc DBA YES watch's website are provided on
an 'as is' basis. Wild Seed Inc DBA YES watch makes no warranties,
expressed or implied, and hereby disclaims and negates all other
warranties including, without limitation, implied warranties or
conditions of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, or
non-infringement of intellectual property or other violation of
rights.
Further,	Wild Seed Inc DBA YES watch does not warrant or make any
representations concerning the accuracy, likely results, or
reliability of the use of the materials on its website or otherwise
relating to such materials or on any sites linked to this site.
4. Limitations
In no event shall Wild Seed Inc DBA YES watch or its suppliers be liable
for any damages (including, without limitation, damages for loss of
data or profit, or due to business interruption) arising out of the
use or inability to use the materials on Wild Seed Inc DBA YES
watch's website, even if Wild Seed Inc DBA YES watch or a Wild Seed
Inc DBA YES watch authorized representative has been notified orally
or in writing of the possibility of such damage. Because some
jurisdictions do not allow limitations on implied warranties, or
limitations of liability for consequential or incidental damages,
these limitations may not apply to you.
5. Accuracy of materials
The materials appearing on Wild Seed Inc DBA YES watch website could
include technical, typographical, or photographic errors. Wild Seed
Inc DBA YES watch does not warrant that any of the materials on its
website are accurate, complete or current. Wild Seed Inc DBA YES
watch may make changes to the materials contained on its website at
any time without notice. However Wild Seed Inc DBA YES watch does not
make any commitment to update the materials.
6. Links
Wild Seed Inc DBA YES watch has not reviewed all of the sites linked to
its website and is not responsible for the contents of any such
linked site. The inclusion of any link does not imply endorsement by
Wild Seed Inc DBA YES watch of the site. Use of any such linked
website is at the user's own risk.
7. Modifications
Wild Seed Inc DBA YES watch may revise these terms of service for its
website at any time without notice. By using this website you are
agreeing to be bound by the then current version of these terms of
service.
8. Governing Law
These terms and conditions are governed by and construed in accordance with
the laws of California and you irrevocably submit to the exclusive
jurisdiction of the courts in that State or location.
Privacy Policy
Your privacy is important to us. It is Wild Seed Inc DBA YES watch's
policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may
collect from you across our website, http://yeswatch.com.
We don't ask for your personal information unless we truly need it.
When we do, we'll only collect what we need by fair and lawful
means and, where appropriate, with your knowledge or consent. We'll
also let you know why we're collecting it and how it will be used.
We don't share your personal information with third-parties, except
where required by law. We will only retain personal information for
as long as necessary to provide you with a service.
We don't store your personal information on our servers unless it's
required for providing a service to you. What we store, we'll
protect within commercially acceptable means to protect your personal
information from loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access,
disclosure, copying, use or modification.
Our Story
30 Day Money Back Guarantee.
Warranty & Repairs
Signup For Special Promotions and Offers
Terms & Conditions / Privacy Policy
Copyright 2020 - YES watch
HomeOur StoryPress ClippingsPractical ApplicationsTestimonialsVideos & LinksContact UsInstruction Manuals1.0 Instruction Manual2.0 Instruction Manual3.0 Instruction Manual4.0 Instruction ManualEQ Instruction ManualV7 Instruction ManualSign Up For Special Offers
Equilibrium SilvertoneEQ SpecificationsEQ AccessoriesEQ City ListingEquilibrium BlackEQ SpecificationsEQ AccessoriesEQ City ListingEQ SpecificationsEQ Instruction ManualEQ AccessoriesBezelsBracelets & StrapsToolsBattery ExchangeEQ City ListingDST standards & TZ mapClassic Steel CollectionsWorldwatch - Cozmo - SolsticeBezelsBracelets & StrapsTime SpecsBattery ExchangeInstruction ManualsClassic Titanium CollectionsZulu - Inca - KundaliniBezelsBracelets & StrapsTime SpecsBattery ExchangeInstruction ManualsThe Tati WatchStrapsTime SpecsBattery Exchange3.0 Instruction ManualThe Luna CollectionBraceletsTime SpecsBattery Exchange3.0 Instruction ManualRepair & WarrantyBattery Exchange
